easypromosapp.com 2015-06-18

# Privacy Policy - Create promotions and contests | Easypromos

**What is personal data?**

Personal data is information about an identifiable individual, as defined by current legislation (such as email data and/or IP address, should these unequivocally identify the user).

**Use and transfer of data**

EASYPROMOS does not make any use of the personal information of users who take part in promotions through our platform, other than that which is strictly required for us to properly provide our services.

EASYPROMOS guarantees that your personal details will not, under any circumstances, be disclosed to third parties or used for sending advertising, or used for any means other than your participation in the promotions carried out through the EASYPROMOS application.

**Unsubscriptions**

Users may, at any time, unsubscribe and request the elimination of their account from their database, exercising their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition, as determined by Law 15/1999 of December 13 and explained in point 4.

**Permissions and Facebook page management**

In order to successfully provide its services, EASYPROMOS needs Facebook's permission to "manage pages". EASYPROMOS can only use this permission to guarantee that the Facebook page administrators can access the private area connected with this page. EASYPROMOS will not make any other use of Facebook's "manage pages" permission and under no circumstances will it be able to make modifications in the Facebook pages that are managed by the administrator.

**EASYPROMOS privacy policy and data protection  
**  
 **1\. Presentation and right to information**

EASYPROMOS takes the protection of your privacy and personal information very seriously. To this end your personal information will be kept secure and treated with the utmost care. Details of users who take part in the promotions WILL NOT, UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES, BE DISCLOSED TO THIRD PARTIES OR USED TO SEND ADVERTISING, OR USED FOR ANY MEANS OTHER THAN THOSE FOR WHICH THE DATA HAS BEEN COLLECTED.

This privacy policy governs the access and use of the service of the website http://www.easypromosapp.com and all EASYPROMOS Facebook applications: Easypromos Basic, Premium and Easypromos White Label apps (hereinafter referred to together as "Website") that EASYPROMOS, S.L., with C.I.F. B-65576878 and located in 17001 Girona, Güell, 58 places at the disposal of its clients.

**2\. Recommendations**

Please read carefully and follow these recommendations:

Use alphanumeric passwords of at least 8 characters in both lower and uppercase on your computers or mobile devices.  
The Website is not aimed at minors. Please exert parental control to prevent or regulate access of minors to the internet and to properly inform children about relevant security issues.  
Keep an up-to-date antivirus program installed on your computer to guarantee it be free of malware and spyware applications that may endanger your internet browsing and the information stored on your computer.  
Read and check the terms of use and the privacy policy on the Easypromos Website.

**3\. Processing personal data and purpose of treatment**

EASYPROMOS meets the requirements of Spanish Law 15/1999 of 13 December regarding Protection of Personal Data (LOPD) and its implemental regulations, as well as the provisions of Law 34/2002 of 11 July, established by the Information Society Services. Your personal details are managed in accordance with the provisions of that legislation, maintaining the technical, organizational and security measures necessary for guaranteeing the confidentiality of the same and preventing alteration, loss, treatment or unauthorized access.

By accepting this Privacy and Data Protection Policy, the user agrees to the Privacy Policy and expressly consents to the automatized processing of personal data provided so that we may offer our services via our Website.

The client/user is informed and lends their consent to the inclusion of their data in EASYPROMOS' existing automatized files, duly registered in the General Registry of Data Protection, and to the authorized treatment of said data.

You authorize and give your express consent to EASYPROMOS for the treatment of your personal details for the purposes described. Such details will be those which you provide or which may be collected in the websites owned by EASYPROMOS, via contact forms, through the sign-up process, or the installation or activation of EASYPROMOS products and applications, and/or via any other means. EASYPROMOS does not solicit sensitive information from the user, as defined by articles 7 and 8 of the LOPD, related to race or ethnic origin, religious belief, criminal record, physical or mental health or sexual orientation.

In order to successfully provide its services, EASYPROMOS needs the Facebook permission "manage pages". Easypromos will only use this permission to guarantee that the Facebook page administers can access the private area connected to this page.

EASYPROMOS will not make any use of the "page management" Facebook permission other than that stated in the previous paragraph and will not, under any circumstances, be able to carry out modifications in those Facebook pages managed by the administrator.

The user data that is collected through the promotions is owned by the administrator of said promotions, with EASYPROMOS being responsible for the treatment of said data for the successful operation and hosting of promotion details. EASYPROMOS undertakes, pursuant to the provisions of article 12.2 of the LOPD, to treat data according to the instructions of the promotion administrator, which is strictly for the provision of contracted services, and not to apply or use the personal data for other means.

EASYPROMOS informs you that the administrator has tools with which to permanently delete data of promotion users.

**4\. Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation and Opposition**

At any time you may exercise your right to access, rectify, cancel and oppose the processing of personal details held by EASYPROMOS, via written request to sales@easypromosapp.com, indicating the subject "Data Protection" and proving your identity in accordance with the provisions of law.

**5\. Minors**

It is forbidden for minors under the age of 14 to purchase products, activate promotions or use EASYPROMOS applications without the proper consent of parents and/or guardians.

EASYPROMOS will not collect personal information from minors under the age of 14 without proper written consent from their parents or guardians. In this case, consent should be sent to EASYPROMOS via sales@easypromosapp.com for verification and authorization.

If, at any time, EASYPROMOS discovers proof of having received data from a minor which does not meet the requirements of regulations, it will proceed to cancel and delete said data.

**6\. Security Measures**

EASYPROMOS maintains levels of personal data protection in accordance with LOPD and ROYAL DECREE 1720/2007, dated 21 December which passed the executive regulation of the LOPD, on Personal Data Protection, and has put in place the technical measures available to it to avoid the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorised access and theft of the data users submit via the website, without prejudice to inform you that internet security measures are not impregnable.

EASYPROMOS agrees to comply with the duty of confidentiality with respect to the personal data contained in the automated file, in accordance with applicable law.

Any transmission of personal data will be made using technology that complies with the appropriate security standards for the protection of your data. Also, we inform you that the hosting service for the data and contents stored in the platform is located within the European Union and that said data is treated in a country which offers an adequate level of protection in the field of data protection. Acceptance of this document implies express and irrevocable authorization for EASYPROMOS to subcontract hosting services, in compliance with article 21 of Royal Decree 1720/2007 of 21 December which approves the Regulations implementing Law 15/1999 of 13 December on the protection of personal data.

**7\. Cookies.**

Our website may use cookies: small data files generated on your computer to streamline navigation and ensure the operation of some of our applications. You have the option to delete and prevent the generation of cookies by selecting the corresponding option in your browser. Upon selecting options relevant to cookies, please note that these files facilitate your internet navigation (by remembering site preferences or language adjustments, for example). You can obtain more information about how cookies work at http://www.youronlinechoices.com/es/. However, note that deactivating these elements may prevent the proper operation of the site in some cases.

**8\. Links to websites**

The EASYPROMOS Website may contain links to websites of third party companies or entities. EASYPROMOS cannot be held responsible for the way in which these companies manage the protection of privacy and personal data, so we recommend you read the privacy statements of these companies that are not property of EASYPROMOS with relation to the use, processing and protection of personal data. The conditions offered by these websites may not be the same as those offered by EASYPROMOS.

**9\. Release of image rights of the promotion winners**

The user accepts that the name and image of the winners of promotions carried out via the EASYPROMOS application may be made public on the EASYPROMOS website and in any other promotional material, globally and without right to renumeration, and for a up to a year from the conclusion of each promotion in which the user participates.

**10\. Cancellation of personal details**

The EASYPROMOS promotions administrator may terminate a promotion at any time, and without cost, from the administration panel. From the moment in which the promotion is terminated any personal details hosted within the EASYPROMOS application will be cancelled and permanently destroyed by EASYPROMOS.

As long as the promotion is not terminated, EASYPROMOS, in their capacity as treatment manager, will house the data within their application in order to successfully provide their services.

**11\. Changes**

EASYPROMOS reserves the right to revise its Privacy Policy at any time it deems appropriate. For this reason, please check this privacy statement regularly in order to read the most recent version of the EASYPROMOS Privacy Policy.
